(David:)This is an amazing woman, Leonard.
She has a curious and agile mind.
(David:)Not to mention being curious and agile
in other respects.
(Penny:)Shut up.
(Leonard:)Yes, please, shut up.
(Leonard:)So, um, Dave, don't you think
you and I should get back to the lab?
(Leonard:)You know, that dark matter
isn't gonna detect itself.
(David:)I was thinking about taking the afternoon
off so I could experiment with Penny.
- Really? We're gonna do an experiment?
DAVID: Uh-huh.
We're gonna explore the effects of tequila
shots on a gorgeous 22-year-old woman.
That's not an experiment.
You saw what happened last night.
DAVID: You ready to go?
- Yeah.
(Penny:)- Oh, can I drive the motorcycle?
- Yeah, why not?
(David:)You can't do any worse than Leonard.
- Oh, my God.
- No, that's good. That's funny.
(Leonard:)By the way, my leg is killing me.
Thanks for asking.